SEAN FISHER

FULL STACK IS DEVELOPER

LANGUAGES

JavaScript | React.JS Node.JS | Express | Axios | Knex SQL | Postgres Solidity | Truffle HTML CSS | Bootstrap

CORE COMPENTANCIES

Test Driven Development | Jest | Mocha | Cypress Programming RESTful APIs Agile Principles Git Workflow

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a highly motivated and professional web developer with extensive work and entrepreneurial experience. I learn quickly and I'm keen to develop my skills and master new frameworks and languages. I love engineering solutions to tough problems and working collaboratively with my team to build amazing projects.

CONTACT INFORMATION

Phone: (562)-568-6707 seankfisher@gmail.com

Linkedin: linkedin.com/in/seankristianfisher

GitHub: github.com/pheadlessg

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

JUNIOR FULL STACK JS DEVELOPER

Northcoders, Manchester, UK | July 2018 - January 2019

Developed full stack web applications using JavaScript, React.JS, Express, Knex and PostgreSQL to demonstrate end to end web app development for training purposes.

Additionally worked on a team learning Solidity and the Truffle framework to develop and launch a DApp on the Ethereum blockchain to demonstrate the issues inherent to online voting. My contribution included project management, creating the smart contract as part of a two-person team and using the Truffle framework to create a React.JS frontend for the project.

COMPANY DIRECTOR / CONSULTANT

Cook:Manchester Ltd., Manchester, UK | July 2013 to Present

Founded, built and managed a commissary kitchen and food business consultancy in Manchester, UK.

Regular day-to-day activities involved digital and physical marketing, facilities management, accounting and sales of services as well as a high level of customer care for all clients.

Consultancy work involves working within a personalised plan with each client to assist them with product costing, product and brand development, food hygiene training, legal advice and market analysis.

Successfully helped many small food businesses in the UK from concept to opening their first permanent locations, some of which are now beginning national expansion.

MICROSOFT DIXONS RETAIL ADVISOR

McCurrach UK | October 2012 to April 2013

Operated as retail tech advisor for Microsoft products across a portfolio of 60 big box stores in the North-West of England.

Oversaw initial staff training, store merchandising and product advocacy during the launch of Windows 8, Office 365 and Microsoft Surface products as well as producing regular high quality reporting on customer feedback and market competition for Microsoft's product line.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF SALFORD, UK 2006-2009

Journalism & English Literature BA

UNIVERSITY OF CANTERBURY, UK 2001-2003

Film Studies BA